drakesoftware.com 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Last updated: 07.19.2018
This Privacy Policy is designed to answer your questions about the information Drake Software
("Drake", "we", "us" or "our") collects on its websites and mobile applications. It applies to the
drakesoftware.com website, and other related websites and mobile applications where this
policy appears in the footer of the page (collectively referred to as the "Sites").
Types of Information We Collect
The information we collect about you falls into the following two categories:
      Personal Information—information that tells us who you are or that provides
      information about you (such as your order history and preferences), and
     Technical Information—information about your visit that is not linked to your identity
The Personal Information we collect when you use our Sites may include your name, mailing
address, phone number, and email address. We request Personal Information when you order a
product or service, use our mobile applications, register for newsletters, participate in certain
promotional activities, fill out surveys, participate in online demonstrations, register for online
training, contact Drake support, engage in bank transactions and correspond with us.
When you visit our Sites, we also collect Technical Information such as the website you visited
before our Site, the pages you visit on our Sites, the website you visit next, the browser you
use, your computer's IP address, and any search terms entered on our Sites. We use cookies
(see section "Use of Cookies") and other technology to collect this data. In general, we do not
connect this Technical Information with the Personal Information we collect from you.
How We Use Information
We use all the information we collect to provide our customers with superior service and a
smooth, efficient, and personalized experience when using our Sites. In particular, we use
information for the following types of activities:
We use Personal Information to fill product orders and service and information requests, send
you order confirmations, administer your account, and send you marketing communications.
For example, we use the information for delivery, payment, and customer service.
We use Technical Information, on an aggregated basis, to understand customer behavior and
demographics, to help run our Sites more efficiently and monitor the level of activity on our
Sites, and to evaluate the effectiveness of our advertising.
                                                                             13567_00/0001/WBK-3326529_4

If you contact us, we may also save your correspondence or comments. We use this
information to help us provide better service in the event you contact us again.
We may also use the information we collect from you to provide you with advertisements
about our products and services on the Sites, on other websites, and through mail and email,
to protect the security and integrity of the Sites and our business, and as otherwise indicated
in our Terms of Use.
Choice/Opt-Out
You may choose to stop receiving our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe
instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at support@drakesoftware.com.
If you choose to stop receiving our marketing emails, we will continue to send you
transactional and relationship email communications as a Drake customer.
Security
Drake maintains reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect your data from loss,
misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction in accordance with this
Privacy Policy. When you make a purchase on the Sites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)
encryption technology to safeguard your credit card information while it is being sent to us.
The SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This
security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock
(depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window.
We take the protection of your data very seriously. All data collected through our Sites is
protected by a secure server. In addition, we use SSL to secure the transmission of data from
the internet to our systems.
All data is maintained and backed-up on a regular schedule to provide adequate redundancy
and ensure that the integrity of information is never jeopardized.
All of our employees are subject to strict guidelines regarding confidentiality, and internal
access to your data is limited to those employees with a business reason for using such data.
All of our employees sign non-disclosure agreements to protect your data. We also take
appropriate disciplinary measures whenever necessary to enforce these rules.
We make every commercially reasonable effort to be fully compliant with the rules under
sections 6713 and 7216 of the Internal Revenue Code.
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where you have chosen a
username and password to access your account and certain parts of the Sites, you are
                                                                            13567_00/0001/WBK-3326529_4

 responsible for keeping this password confidential. In the event that you believe your
 password has been compromised, please contact us at support@drakesoftware.com.
 No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100%
 secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Information Sharing
 In general, we disclose Personal Information and/or Technical Information to other companies
 for only the following reasons:
 - to assist credit card processors and other companies that perform services for us and who
     have agreed not to use any of our information for any other purpose, or
 - to assist a government investigation, verification or similar purposes, if required by law,
     subpoena or court order, or as otherwise necessary for fraud prevention or to maintain the
     security and integrity of the Sites and our business, or
 - as needed to enforce our Terms of Use, or
 - if a company purchases our business or assets.
 Affiliates and Third-Party Providers
 We do not sell, rent, or lease your Personal Information to affiliates or third parties.
 We partner with third-party companies that provide related products and services such as tax
 refund settlement products, audit protection and workflow automation tools. When you enroll
 for these services or products of a third party with which we conduct business, and with your
 specific consent, we will share your Personal Information to the extent necessary for the third
 party to provide such products or services. These parties are not granted permission to use
 personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing these services.
 We may, from time to time, email you about related products and services offered by
 our affiliates and carefully selected partners. In those cases, your Personal Information
 (such as e-mail address, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred by us to
 the affiliate or the third party. If you do not wish to receive future emails about these
 products and services, you can unsubscribe or opt out by clicking on the opt out link at
 the bottom of the applicable email, and we will make every effort to process your
 request within ten (10) business days. If you choose to opt out of these emails about
 related products and services, we will continue to send you transactional and
 relationship email communications as a Drake customer.
 Use of Cookies
 A "cookie" is a small text file transferred by a website or mobile applications to your
 computer's hard drive. We send cookies when you browse our Sites, make purchases, respond
 to online surveys or polls, or request information. Accepting the cookies used on our Sites does
 not give us access to your Personal Information, but we can use the cookies to identify your
                                                                               13567_00/0001/WBK-3326529_4

computer. The aggregate information collected permits us to analyze traffic patterns on our
Sites. This can enable us over time to provide you with a better experience on our Sites by
improving the content and making them easier to use. For example, cookies can keep track of
what you have selected to purchase as you continue to shop and allow you to enter your
password only once on pages where a login is required.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies or selectively
accept certain cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies,
there may be some features of our Sites that will not be available to you and some web pages
may not display properly.
Links to other Websites
Our Sites may contain links to third-party websites. Please be aware that Drake is not
responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be
aware when they leave our Sites and to read the privacy policies of each and every website
that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the
information collected by the Sites of Drake and no other sites.
Social Media Features
Our Sites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may
collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Sites, and they may set a cookie
to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either
hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Sites. Your interactions with these
features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.
Do Not Track Signals
There is no uniform or consistent standard or definition for responding to, processing, or
communicating Do Not Track signals. At this time, our Sites do not function differently based
on a user’s Do Not Track signal. For more information on Do Not Track signals, see All About
Do Not Track (https://allaboutdnt.com/).
Children's Privacy
Our Sites are not targeted at children of any age, and we do not collect information from
children under age 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a
child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.
                                                                             13567_00/0001/WBK-3326529_4

Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information
Drake acknowledges that you have the right to access your Personal Information. Upon request,
we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal
Information. To review, update or amend your Personal Information, or to request
deletion of your Personal Information, or to request that we no longer use your Personal
Information to provide you services, you may contact us at support@drakesoftware.com.
We will make every effort to respond to your request within 30 days.
We will retain and use your Personal Information for as long as your account is active, or
as needed to provide you services, or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations,
resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Changes to this Privacy Notice
If there are changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here. Please
be sure to check this page occasionally. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, such
as changes in the way we use or disclose Personal Information, we will provide you with notice
of the change and a chance to choose not to have your information used or disclosed under
the revised Privacy Policy. By using the Sites, you are deemed to have accepted any changes to
this Privacy Policy.
General Data Protection Regulation
The General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"), a regulation in European Union ("EU") law,
is a new set of rules that changes the way personal data of individuals inside the European
Economic Area ("EEA") can be collected and processed. Among other things, the law can apply
to non-EU companies who are offering goods or services to persons inside the EEA. Drake takes
the privacy and security of its customers, and of any person whose data Drake handles, very
seriously. Drake does not sell personal data to third parties, and follows stringent data privacy
and cyber security protocols to protect the personal data it handles. However, the GDPR is a
unique set of regulations particular to EU law, and does not mesh well with the current
framework in the United States.
Drake is headquartered in Franklin, North Carolina in the United States. Our Sites and services
are hosted and administrated in the United States or hosted with cloud service providers who
are headquartered in the United States. Drake's target users are in the United States. Drake
does not currently intend to offer goods or services to individuals in the European Union. If you
are located in the European Union, or anywhere outside of the United States, be aware that
information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of our Sites and services
may be processed in, transferred to, and stored in the United States and will be subject to
United States law. The privacy and data protection laws of the United States may be different
from the laws of your country of residence.
                                                                             13567_00/0001/WBK-3326529_4

With the implementation of GDPR, we are taking further steps to ensure that any potential
customers understand that Drake does not intend to sell its goods or services to persons inside
the EEA. These include limiting access to certain web-based services when attempting to access
from within EU borders.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or concerns about Drake's use of your information or about this
Privacy Policy, please write or email us at the address below:
Drake Software
235 East Palmer St
Franklin, NC (USA) 28734
Email: privacy@drakesoftware.com
                                                                         13567_00/0001/WBK-3326529_4
